We hope you're having a great time in san francisco.
Thanks for attending build.
And, welcome to the...session.
Can we see a show of hands how many of you have work with media capture before?
Great.
Know-how many of you have submitted a camera app to the store.
To see some of you and we're here to get more of you onboard.
And, this session will show you
...how easy it is to develop powerful camera apps
for windows term.
Mike will join us later in the session.
I want to remind you that would be great to have your feedback once you
are session is done please don't forget about that.
As you heard in the keynote and various other sessions convergence of api
is across various device form factors is a key theme this year.
You can now build your app once.
And, run it on all your windows devices.
Will begin
by covering some of the new functionality that you can leverage starting with windows down?
And, in order to get you started easily we have
some great universal windows platform samples.
That michael walk us through later in the session.
As part of convergence where
combine the functionality of windows media capture also known as wm
see and windows phone media capture also known as w
pm see into w mc.
So, features that are only available for...device form factor
of now available across all windows devices.
For example, video stabilization comes from pc.
While get...frame comes from phone.
Both of them are now available in all devices.
This slide here shows a list of the functionality that you can leverage starting
that windows stem features that are...with an asterisk.
...available only on devices that
ship with windows stem support for this features is discoverable through a property.
And, this session
will cover the first five in this list through code samples on demos.
First let's take a look at software bitmap.
Software bitmap is a data
object representing image data and provides access to pixels.
It has very good interop with many of the consumers on producers which
...in the next slide.
As you can see in this picture software...can reproduced from
...file stream using bitmap decoder
all from the camera through captured frame.
You can also create your own software roadmap in the desired pixel format and size.
Will soon start providing support for software...
And, once that happens all the effects
...that library can be used you can also create your own custom
affects by getting access to the pixels the same code them can be used
...video stream using I basic video
effect which was covered in the audio and video creation session on witness...
From...point of view.
You can save...software roadmap to a file.
Are stream using the bitmap encoder are
this plate on the screen using example software bitmap source object?
Currently...is not displayed correctly
...small issue rest showed this will be fixed in our next flight.
You'll
be seeing software bitmap in use in one of the samples that we demonstrate later in the session.
This samples that are available today for you.
Should cover most of
the immediate functionality related to capture scenarios on-camera functionality?
Many more samples...and will appear on get...
And, this session-level...focusing more on the first three samples in this list.
Preview frames are very fast...because the
Minimal image processing this is very useful
for applications that do live analysis, for example.
Live translation services barcode cure code detection etc.
The get preview frame sample.
Shows you how to get access to the current review as a video frame object.
also handles device rotation and media capture lifecycle management.
Michael show this an action and take us...review let's invite mike.
They just...the for the introduction
hello everyone my name is mike and I'll be walking you through some of our samples.
So, there's let-me prepare you for this.
There is a lot of content in the samples
...that josie here and.
I could I could spend hours here with you talking about creating camera apps
and all the cool things that you can do in this space.
But, there's also a lot of great stuff going on later at build that I want to remiss so this creates a little bit of
an internal conflict in me but I am going to have to keep it short.
And, that means skipping over some parts of the code like some of
our helper methods and some of our...handlers and also skipping over
demo ing each of the samples on each of the devices but all...samples like
sandeep set are available for you...right now so if you haven't done so yet please
...clone are samples repository...the samples on your own devices
ok so let's get started and I'm going to start by showing you the
...sample just to give you an idea for what it is that it does and...look for each
...get preview frame.
Right there.
And, you'll see it launches straight to the preview which means that it's taken care of initialize
in the media capture and configuring it for use and it also
handles device orientations so any time I rotate my device.
The preview adjusts so that it always rains upright we
received feedback from you guys that.
This wasn't the easiest thing to figure out so we wanted
to make sure that the sample you have a good starting point for rotation as well.
So, I'm going to tap the get previous frame button right here.
And, you'll see that next to it a text
...is populated with the dimensions and the pixel format of the frame.
Now on the linear six thirty right here that happens to be...btwelve
by default but keep in mind that may vary by device.
Now the api does offer and overload that allows you to specify the picture
format it'll perform the conversion for you and the sample
makes use of that when we choose to show the frame in...
There we go the current preview frame is now display to the right
of the preview and just below it you can see that the pixel format has changed.
Now as we...familiarize
yourselves with the software bitmap which is the underlying object doing all of
this we included some code that edits the pixels on the software bitmap to
apply a simple green effect and also some code they'll say the frame
to disk...give...a try.
That's it by the way you can you can have a lot of fun creating your own custom effects if you haven't done so
before give this a try come up with their own algorithms it's actually a lot of fun.
So, let me show you let me show you the code behind all this.
Get preview frame is the method on the media capture so we're going to start looking in this region.
And, the method is doing all this is right here.
let me scroll over and you'll see that the first thing we're doing is we're getting information
about the previous stream at the moment and that is because we're going to use the with and
the height of the preview along with our desired pixel format.
To create this video frame which describes the assault that will get from the get
pre frame api we...into the api.
Will return as an object that contains a software bitmap?
And, that software bitmap right there is our previous frame at this point we're basically done that was all we
had to do now to show you a couple more things that we can do with this we go ahead and populate
...text block that you saw with
the dimensions with height and the picture format of the frame.
And, then depending on the state of the
...check boxes we edit the pixels we show the frame
in the ui and we can save the frame to...now let's
...the mentioned before there is a small issue with displaying.
The software bitmap source in...right now so,
for now you might want to use this little work around the...here for you but because we have
the fix ready and it's just waiting for the next slide to reach all you guys.
You might as well go with of recommended pattern for that don't worry we will update
...samples as soon as a fixes out.
So, because we just cover to get previous frame and there's a couple more things here that I want to show you
...rotation for a while.
In this sample.
use the display information object to receive orientation change notifications.
Windows trigger.
We go in apply the corrective rotation
to the preview and for this sample I will show you exactly what the helper methodist doing.
So, in the case that we're dealing with
an external camera there's no work for us to do the assumption is a
cameras connected over usd is probably not being subjected to the same rotations that
the actual devices but otherwise we graphic current orientation
of display and we convert it to a number of degrees now if the previews being mirror
...and I'll talk more about that in a moment we need to match
that mirroring by basically inverting rotation and once we've done all of that we
can get the current media stream properties of the preview.
At the information about the rotation to them and then set them on the
preview this is the way we recommend you guys to preview rotation because it
says it's a lot of work it's not actually doing pixel rotation
is not applying that transformation to the frames it's just adding the rotation information as pure
metadata which means the actual rotation work is being deferred
we later until much closer to rendering and if you think about it you
could be running the preview at http.
Or higher thirty frames
per second that's a lot of churn to be applying this transformation to all of those frames.
So, because this api was available on phone before I
wanted to demo it on my laptop as well and I have it ready for
you here and you'll see the ad you I looks pretty much the same as on the phone
...universal apps.
It also behaves pretty much the same notice it
is a different format because it is a different device and we can choose to show the frame
...also edit the pixels right away the goal green effect of that is very unflattering
...it...let's try for another one.
All right let's just let's...that you'll see you'll see that there's
something a little weird going on and what is that?
I'm raising one hand on one side and the preview frame shows the other
site being raced that is because
...preview mirroring here now I'm raising my left
and right now and on the live previous...to you a kind of looks like I'm raising my
right-hand that's because you're on the other side of the display for me looks the preview behaves exactly like
amer...something a users have come to expect from camera apps
...from facing camera is just a lot easier to fix your hair check your
te for something if the preview is behaving like amer.
All right so I think that's all I have for you...brings in the back in.
So, let's now...about the camera capture sample.
So, the camera capture sample is a great starting point for
capture scenarios and it's very easy to extend it basically
approach to the functionality of photon video capture along with the along with a
live video preview it also allows you to do concurrent photon
video record if the device supports it.
It also handles device rotation and manages your.
Lifetime management of the media capture just like the get previous frame
sample.
So, michael take...into...on this as well excellent.
Switch back computer.
And, again,
I'll start off by showing you the sample itself we called this one the universal
...sample that's also the name that you'll find...for
...in our samples repository and you'll see this time the preview is a
nice full-screen preview with overlaid semi transparent buttons we went all-out in the
ui for this one and,
there's to capture buttons on the site so let's give...a try this have you smil right there.
All right beautiful and I'm going to record...short video as well
in japan across the stage.
There we go the lighting is really not working for us here that's fine.
Now you'll notice the other capture button disappears when I'm using one of them
caroline for later.
This sample actually shares a lot of code with get preview
...sample and later on when you have a closer look at the samples you will find
...similarities there are no
to major differences the first one of course is a types of captures that we're doing we're
caption photos and videos as opposed to getting preview frames and the
second one is the way we handle the orientations scenarios and let-me demo that right now.
So, you'll see.
That when I rotate the device the buttons always remain on the same edge of the screen.
Just like the navigation buttons at the bottom they just rotate in
place.
To adapt and remain operate so let me start by showing you the code to do that.
We're setting up or you why in one of our helper functions.
We declare and
...rotation preference and you can think of this as a rotation
...within your app now it may not always be granted
and the reason for this is that there's, there's
situations are scenarios like the desktop where you can have multiple apps and
one app shouldn't really prevent your whole environment from rotating or, you know,
not matching the orientation of everything else so even though we're declaring this
on multi app almost absent areas we still need to subscribe to those events to the
orientation changed events and you'll find two different kinds for those in the sample.
The first one we seen already it's a display information orientation change this is part of the
similarities that this sample...with the get previous, for example,
and, this will trigger whenever you see that rotation animation going on
...platform does...before it updates the layout for your page.
And, the other one this is what's the what's new here is the
orientation sensor and this one will trigger regardless of whether orientation
...engage are not regardless of whether the
auto rotation preference is being honored or not and this is a method that we're
using to update the orientation of our buttons.
So, all of this code is already implemented here seo articles
look later on leverage it for your own apps if you think about it keeping the
buttons on the same edge of the screen is basically the same experience...camera app gives
you so it might be a little more familiar for users it's something for you to consider.
So, let's get this can over to the to the actual capture
site now and we'll start by looking at how to take a photo.
And, here's a little trick on
a show you remember when we were doing capture.
That one of the buttons always disappeared were capturing photo video disappeared
were capturing video the...buttons appear to...
many windows devices support capturing photos and videos at the same time.
The linear six thirty right here being an entry-level device
...not support that but finding out if that is supporter not on the...your
...running on is easy...reading this property.
Now if you want to take this to the next level you should really have a look at the camera profile
sample.
That will show you how to do concurrent capture with multiple cameras
at the same time or for more granularity
...can tell you exactly what combinations of for solutions are
supporter for simultaneous photo and video capture so
...will talk more about that later anyway let's get back to thinking of photo.
You can see here that we're capturing...choicestream in
the jpeg format and then at the same time while we're doing this capture
we're getting the current orientation of the camera and.
We...current orientation and the stream to...to a helper method
...combine both and save in two-a jpeg file in the
picture library this jpeg file will support multiple orientations because of
this now recording a video is even easier.
We start by creating...
storage file we create our encoding profile for the video in this case mp
for and then same patterns before we get the current orientation of
the camera we apply that to our encoding profile directly.
And, then we can just start recording...video encoding profile with the
encoding profile to the storage file there's no need for any
cover methods I will do all of that rotation and file saving here.
Now because we're doing video recordingwe recommend you subscribe to the
record limitation exceeded event of the media capture you'll find that under
our event handlers right there this is the
vendor will trigger as a way to notify your app that it has exceeded
the maximum length for a single session limited set at three...which
should be enough for most users to capture anything that they wanted to get in a single
take but this is how you can prepare your app for that scenario and you'll see here
we are stopping video recording at this point and updating
argue I to reflect this but you might want to go that extra step and try to start a
new recording session so that your users stone promise anything that they may have wanted to capture.
Another media capture event that is interesting is
...media capture failed event and this will trigger for of a variety of errors
but most importantly when your users unplug the camera a
usb camera while it's being used so all of the samples you'll see here today handle this
in the same basic way the...the error clean-up and resources app
may still be in use and opted the...to reflect the cameras no longer...use again,
you might want to go that extra step and...error message asking your...behave
...them why do they...camera and unplug the camera, you know, stuff like that.
What we're talking about events...something else,
you know, that windows phones have a two-stage camera shutter button on the...many of them
...for camera application this is very interesting you
can subscribe to events coming from that button and I'll show you how to do that.
The first thing you need to do is go over to your project references and add a reference.
...you'll find under windows universal extensions and it's a mobile
x window microsoft mobile extension sdk for universal app platform what
...make sure that has a check park next.
Click okay and right here where we register all of our event handlers.
You can see that were checking to see if that type is present on the device that
we're running on this differentiates phones from windows you'll note that there are sorry
phones from desktops and tablets note that there is no pound defines or if
there avce or even separate projects for this so it's
a much more streamline coding experience and what you may have seen before?
If there's if this type is available...register for events such as the camera
...button...camera
pressed and camera released allow you to do cool things like triggering auto
focus on half-price or recording a video only while the shutter button is completely
held down or even capturing photo sequence a burst shot.
This was a lot of stuff so let me do a quick recap of
we looked at we started by talking about
rotation and how there's two objects that are delivering the information that we need to
...scenarios...display information class and the simple orientations
...then we moved over to the captures and we saw how to take a photo how
to recorder video and support multiple orientations multiple aspirations?
After that we went over and looked at the recording at the events that the
media capture races that any camera application should handle record limitation exceeded
and media capture failed and finally the.
Shutter button events the hardware shutter...events that are just so interesting for
...scenarios so all of these are basic features that any camera application
...cover and we already implemented them here for you guys to learn from
...leverage straight in your projects
thank you thank you mike for the detailed explanation.
The beauty of these samples is that there are highly extensible.
We invite you to take this samples and customize them to your needs
rather than reinventing the wheel our next sample demonstrates this extensibility.
The face detection sample is a simple on direct extension of the camera
...sample.
It showcases how easy it is to add face detection all you need to
do is...affect and listen to an event.
On...devices will also enable face based auto focus on
auto explosion so the pictures that you're taking our well let.
Michael demonstrate this extension.
Okay, guys this is my favorite part of
...presentation sandeep said I'm...be showing you how easy it is to
add face detection to your camera app and again let's just fire up the sample.
...looks.
There's that unflattering angle...anyway recognise the
...from the previous sample that we saw the basic capture buttons on this site plus the addition of
a new faces action button on the other site...see how it works.
We go all blue on blue might not work so well but you can see the rectangle...on my face as
I move around it's tracking me so let's bring sandeep in can-you come into the frame
...up there we go so we're tracking multiple faces and you'll see that
there's two different shades of blue being used here and I'll explain why in a moment.
So, jumping into the code now.
There's basically two things that we need to do in our example
table face detection we decided to add a button that's the first thing...button will enable and
the sable the effect the second thing we need to do is
...some sort of control that will...all of the face detection
...boxes we went with the canvas called
faces canvas and you'll notice that it's actually wrapped in a second canvas
...is because it makes it easier for us to deal with things such as rotation
or letter boxing of the preview is a previous stream doesn't match the
aspect ratio off the screen that is being displayed on the size of your window basically.
Now as for the code there's three things that we need to do we need to
enable face detection we need to handle the face detection events and
we need to clean it up so let's look at how to enable it first.
...for doing it's right here and
we start off by creating of face detection effect definition and effective
...is an object that allows you to
set some of the properties on the effect they need to be said before the effect is actually created,
for example, we choose not to run face detection synchronous
...because we wouldn't want to delay any preview frames just because the face detection...running on them.
Then we sets then we have the face detection effect two-run in high-performance
...over the other two precepts that we offer
which are high-quality and the balanced preset.
So, after we've done this we can add the face detection effect
to the pipeline and we're adding it to the video preview
face detection is an effect that you would want to run on the preview most of the time this will actually return you
an instance to the actual effect and all that affect you can subscribe to the face
...event you can set a minimum detection interval in case you want
to space out the events and maybe go a little later on the resources and finally you
can enable face detection and ur detecting faces at this point now
face detection enabling it can be as little sfour lines of code you don't need
to all of this but I just wanted to show you some of the properties that you can play around with now
before we go over and look at the face detection events on a show you how to clean-up face detection when you're done with it.
As you can see is also pretty simple in fact if, you know, you'll be using face
detection again shortly you can get away with just disabling it and then re enabling
it later which...of the work of reconfiguring it and re adding it to the pipeline.
Okay, we get to see the face detection events now.
And, I'm going to give you a little warning this is what makes the bulk of the
code this is because there's a lot of ui calculations being down here
that are completely optional you get all the benefits of the face
detection effect namely automatic exposure and
faces focus just by enabling the effect you don't need to highlight the
faces in the ui but it's a pretty cool thing to do so
I'll show you how that's being done.
You can see that were asking the dispatcher to update ru ip running
this helper method on the list of detected faces that the event
...to us and this is another helper method that I will go into detail.
The first thing it does is of course
clear any existing rectangles from the faces canvas these are rectangles
ave remained from the previous event that we've received so we throw all of those
away and then for each face that we've received we first
of all convert the coordinates of the face box which is the bounding
...on the face from existing in terms of the preview resolution to
existing in terms of the size of our capture element which is our preview control in the
y and we need to do this because there's probably going to be a scaling factor
between the two it's rare that...preview will run at the exact resolution
that it's being displayed on the screen this is nothing too complicated it's basically direct
grabbing each property of the facebook dividing it by the corresponding dimension of the
previous stream which gives you a relative value between zero and one which you can then
multiply by the size of your capture element in the ui so once all
that is done we just choose what we want our face
detection right-angle the highlight part to look like we're
...a stroke any color and right...where you can see where special casing the
first face this is where the two different shades of blue came from and that's because the first phase
that you received in this event is what we call the most important
...in the scene it's the phase that will drive automatic exposure...drive continues
...focus to focus on that person so after we've done that we add
...to the canvas the...being highlighted.
And, finally if you remember from the get
preview frame sample I mention that we're not actually applying rotation to
the preview pixels all of that is being done downstream so any
rotation meta data that we've added to the previous stream we need to match that rotation
on the faces canvas and this is a reason why it was wrapped in...another canvas
...salmon when I showed you that so hopefully that makes a little more sense now
it makes it makes just calculations in this method are easier to deal with.
I think that's all I have for you for this sample.
...pretty cool clear wrong with it what do you think
about-face samoa.
The goal feature.
Let's move on to another...feature.
So, prior to windows stem.
If users if app developers wanted to add
...resume functionality to the app does not possible
the basically had to create of capture multiple videos and
mods them separately now how platform support to...
on resume recording before finalizing it it's very simple.
Just need to call the.
...switch over here sorry we didn't switch are so
positive recording is that so, it's very simple.
All you need to do is called the pauses
think api for the pause functionality and resume
missing ppi for the resume functionality we'll show a live demo
...an action right now so what I'm going to do for this demo is something a little different.
I'll show you one of our internal testing apps and...starch.
...recording over shear.
Ok, there we go so
I'm panning and panning and let's find sandeep various.
Okay, just...recording right there.
Sandeep steps out we record a little more.
...so I'm going to show you the videos well what's great about possum resume is
that it gives you very low latency that
...event is happening exactly when you want.
Okay, we got rotation working...other captures.
All right you'll see the video playing back.
...sandeep gains...to disappear
So, as you can see this feature enables those fund edit as you record scenario
scenarios are becoming so popular now that sharing videos is so prevalent and,
...even though it's as simple api to use it still gives you control over whether you want that
very low latency or whether you want to be a little easier on the resources so,
when you look at msdn pay attention to the
behavior parameter that you pass into the...method thank you?
Thank you...what you over...
Ok, so, now let's move on
move to another feature that is more powerful than the features that we have
...so far video civilization so.
We destabilization can be enabled very similar
to face detection all you need to do is in
the affect configured recommended resolution and start recording.
We'll show you a demo video.
Showcasing the stability achieved through video stabilization
for the demo we capture the scene using to entry-level phones
setup side-by-side on this evaluation rig one of the
phones has...
turned on the other doesn't have it on let's take a look at the demo video now.
Folks.
Node that this is running in realtime on an entry-level device.
That's impressive.
So, we'll covered the first
five features in this list already me step back and say that if you're working
on a feature that is not supported on a device that you have.
You can get started with emulator.
Let's focus on the rest of the features briefly.
Video frame is a data object closely related to software
bitmap and basically carries time stamps.
It is more.
in scenarios where you have a video stream and you have a continuous flow of pictures.
So, it can also represent cpu memory as well as cpu memory.
...geo-tagged helper in api that allows you to tag and
image with the current geo location of the device even when the
requesting app has been suspended are closed.
This is very useful because the geo location service can take a
long-time up to thirty seconds to written the current location
and by the time the user may how suspended app after capturing a picture basically.
Variable photo sequence
also map to specify bracketed shots for capture.
And, this is a very fundamental block in computational photography scenarios.
This was available only on the phone earlier and now it's
available on our windows devices.
We have recede feedback from many of you
that creating a flashlight application needs access to camera
and consumes unnecessary resources.
Have acted on that feedback and now you can control the lamp also known as
flash?
Without access to camera on supported windows...devices.
Michael alluded to this feature earlier.
The camera profiles is a great way to make the most of your
camera it helps you with the fine-grain this code
ability of the concurrent capabilities of a device.
For example, let's say there's a device that can support
...resolution when one of the camera is active.
And, if it cannot support four-k but can only support
up to nntp when both front and back cameras are active.
In the past such devices did not advertise before
...resolution but now it's possible
thanks to profiles where you can discover under what conditions which resolutions are available.
Smoot zoom allows a nice gradual transition to the target zoom
factor.
Rather than a direct zoom which sometimes can be jarring.
In the past hops emulated this by.
Calling resume api multiple times...small steps this
is now supported by the platform...is done in a performant manner.
High dynamic range video is also available on supported windows
...devices.
You might notice that high dynamic range photo is not listed here the list
Shows the api is that can be found in...available today we're working
on advance capture photo api that covers high dynamic range photo.
It will be available when windows townships if not earlier.
Sq video recording is a great use case scenario for
...instagram apps.
And, we have enabled that.
This is enabled in a much more
performant manner and apps don't how to.
Do a lot of work to
...and do the cropping its supported natively by the platform now?
...analysis affect can help them enabling...
Automatic capturing of good pictures balancing between
...are and cases where you don't need...analysis
gives you an indication of when it is useful to capture picture
using hdf it also provides some of the information on the camera's
sensor such as exposure level iso values and many more details.
Finally we also done work to enabler enterprise customers to
set policies that control access to camera we hope you can leverage all of these
and basically get started with the samples that we
have available today we are excited about this and we hope
you are to please welcome mike to say a few final words.
...thank you for coming to build thank you for coming to the...session as you saw we've
done some samples in a different way the break-away from
our usual format of using the sdk template and,
this is something that's new for us so we're very interested in hearing
your feedback to samples like this a cover into and scenarios that behave almost like
real apps are they are they helping you are is this a good model to
carry for work so give us that feedback sandeep and I will be at the
insiders lounge for the next hour and a half and later on at the experts
own from one fifteen until three pm when everyone's packing up you'll still
find us over there so, come over have a chat with us maybe play with the samples for
a little bit now if you if you can't make it or if you're watching online
then I invite you all to go on the msdn forums engage
with us engage with each other give us feedback talk to us about the camera
...stuff that you like to see if you if you have really pressing feedback I want to all
...email send us centers...and build camera at microsoft-dot-com
your reach indeed your reach media reach the entire camera api team.
So, let us know what your developer experiences like let us know the things that you think...it
...to keep doing the things that you think.
Go ahead.
Let's say we have a question from the audience.
To somewhat related questions but early argued
mention that was now the possibility of doing multiple calmer capture
...desktop device or laptop tablet
...any reasonable restriction to the number of see usb cameras that you
can connect it depends on the device capability so,
you know, the...sop also needs to support that if the
...supports it and it's advertised it should be
possible so that's where the camera profiles feature comes into picture the other questions
you have is a number of your start things like the each...video and the
like required windows ten device I assume that does not
mean say nokia fifteen twenty with that's been updated to windows
ten it means a new device correct so the question would be what would be the
first windows ten device phone that we could get tested out
of hardware we cannot disclose that yet but you'll soon hear about it
gift-giving try give the emulator a try we've updated with a lot of the features that are
available on windows ten launch devices so that you can get a headstart with developing
your solution before you can finally get one of those devices that we are also very excited about
...thank you just a question with the face detection
...does api offer any exposure to the decomposition
...eigenvalues or whatever's use so that you can do facial analysis not
...but we're certainly welcome to hear from your
use scenarios and then we'll work to enable the
...email and email recap later if you have time?
The seen analysis give you any information about
...follicular detection your not yet right now right now it is doing the high dynamic range.
Prediction basically but the plan is the scene analysis as a component to
expand on what capabilities task basically so great-great suggestion thank you.
...I want to know the...dieter of
...videos so it's a video you need to use
heidi.
Exposure and road tx process so how do you gets.
Once forty-one...sure so are you talking about
...video of hd photo video...video so difference on
the sensor underneath so that can be different technologies enabling...video so,
depending on the censor, you know, it can be either of those,
... it can be a sensor that is able to capture both low explosion
exposure the same time or it does some sort of a bracketing basically but,
that's the device level variation
...the platform level you don't have to deal with any of that all you do
is the z the control that you go on enable and then if the device supports that you're getting history
...video...a possible solution for this would be
interleaving each role to expose at a different level...and that
...need to run your can video capture at three times a frame rate and varying the exposure in-between
...by...and approach okay.
...question and dual camera dual...will be able to
support dual camera let's take the offline.
...might be a better person for the whole...team instead of a camera api team.
Sorry could you could...at least one camera right definitely but that's
a promise of universal...
Right how many more...other things we can discuss later with.
...sdk provide cropping
...stabilizing the alignment, yeah, and, like
...received capture...by
...anything like that so the video stabilization feature if you want to get
...a crop format you can get that it's your choice as an app developer
...you wanted back into the full resolution that came in you can have
that's where the recommended resolution comes
and we recommend resolution but you're not required to go with that basically this is more for image
like you want to capture receipt and online it and I
said so it's not supported image level it's mainly for the video at this
...I don't I don't think we're talking about visualization here...
For...image stabilization...he's talking about your allows us
...processing images...images so...sdk has
api is that you can leverage to in online images if you are interested in that, yeah,
and, as soon as...publish...update you can keep all your data in the software
bitmap and pusher on to the different components that will offer you the functionality that you're asking about.
What please don't forget earlier session all right these...thank you?